Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Swimming-men
    - Photographs
      - Digital Files
        - 2003/04
          - 2003/04 Head Shots, Take 2 (Box 161)
            (photographs, color head shots)
          - 2003/04 NCAA Championships (Box 161)
          - 2003/04 Men's Swim Team (Box 161)
            (photographs, posed and of national championship trophy for platform diving)
          - 2003/04 MSD Miscellaneous (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots, facilities, meet action; doc files of releases and bios)
          - 2003/04 Media Guide (Box 161)
        - 2004/05
          - 2004/05 Headshots (Box 161)
          - 2004/05 SDM Team Shots (Box 161)
            (photographs, posed, team)
          - 2004/05 Practice (Box 161)
            (photographs, action)
            (includes photo's of members of women's swim team)
          - 2004/05 Trophies (Box 161)
            (photographs, NCAA national championship trophy and 2004 Olympic gold medal)
          - 2004/05 UM vs. Northwestern (Box 161)
            (by Eric Bronson)
          - 2004/05 UM vs. Eastern Michigan University (Box 161)
          - 2004/05 UM vs. Indiana University (Box 161)
          - 2004/05 NCAA Championships, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            (meet action)
          - 2004/05 Guide (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots, meet action; pdf file of media guide)
          - 2004/05 MSD (Box 161)
            (pdf files of releases, media guide, programs, and results)
          - 2004/05 Men's Swim Guide Covers, eps files of media guide covers, eps files will only open on Mac OS (Box 161)
          - 2004/05 Men's Swim Guide Covers (Box 161)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Michigan Athletes in International Swimming Hall of Fame (Box 43)
  - Tennis-men
    - Media Guides
      - 1938 1940-42 (Box 38)
      - 1955, 1957, 1959-1968 (Box 38)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 38)
      - 1973-1985 (Box 38)
      - 1986-1994 (Box 38)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 38)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 38)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 38)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 38)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 38)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous
      - "The Michigan Tennis Complex Program Statement (Box 38)
      - "An Historical record: University of Michigan Tennis" (Box 38)
        (student paper by Timothy P. Madden)
      - Clippings on Barry McKay and 1955-1959 teams (Box 14)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        (Team photos, from Ath. Dept. and other collections are available online in Bentley Image Bank.)
        - Prints
          - 1902, 1939-1941, 1957-1958, 1976-1978, 1982, 1984-1986, 1988-2000 (Box 38)
          - 2000/01-2001/02 (Box 38)
          - 1957 (Box 7)
        - Negatives
          - 1973 (Box 38)
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - Coaches (Box 38)
        - Facilities (Box 38)
        - 1920-1949 (Box 38)
        - 1950-59 1962 (Box 38)
        - 1967-1969 (Box 38)
        - 1970-1971, 1977 (Box 38)
          (negs. & cs)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 38)
        - 1980/81 (Box 38)
        - 1981/82 (Box 38)
        - 1982/83 (Box 38)
        - 1983/84 (Box 38)
        - 1984/85 (Box 38)
        - 1985/86 (Box 38)
        - 1986/87 (Box 38)
        - 1987/88 (Box 38)
        - 1988/99 (Box 38)
          (includes Arthur Ashe contact sheets)
        - 1989/90 (Box 38)
        - 1990/91 (Box 38)
        - 1991/92 (Box 38)
        - 1992/93 (Box 38)
        - 1993/94 (Box 38)
        - 1994/95 (Box 38)
        - 1995/96 (Box 38)
        - 1996 (Box 38)
        - 1996/97 (Box 38)
        - 1997/98 (Box 38)
        - 1998/99 (Box 38)
        - 1999/2000 (Box 38)
          (cs, negatives, print, head shots, posed)
        - 2000/01 (Box 38)
          (cs, match action, posed)
        - 2001/02 (Box 38)
          (cs, prints, head shots, match action, posed)
        - 2002/03 (Box 38)
          (cs, digital cs, negatives, prints, head shots, posed)
        - 2003/04 (Box 38)
          (cs, head shots, posed)
        - Unidentified and undated photographs (Box 38)
        - 2000/01-2003/05 (Box 161)
          (cds of photos, mostly for cs listed above)
        - 2004/05, 1 volumes (Box 255)
          (cds and cs, team headshot and game action)
        - 2005/06, 1 volumes (Box 255)
        - 2006/07, 1 volumes (Box 255)
        - 2007/2008, 1 volumes (Box 255)
    - Meet Programs / Results
      - 1962 (Box 117)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 117)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 117)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 117)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 117)
      - 1977 (Box 117)
      - 1978 (Box 117)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 117)
      - 1981/82 (Box 117)
      - 1982/83 (Box 117)
      - 1983/84 (Box 117)
      - 1984/85 (Box 117)
      - 1985/86 (Box 117)
      - 1986/87 (Box 117)
      - 1987/88 (Box 117)
      - 1988/89 (Box 117)
      - 1989/90 (Box 117)
      - 1990/91 (Box 117)
      - 1990/91, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - 1991/92, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - 1992/93, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - 1993/94, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - 1994/95 (Box 118)
      - 1995/96, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - 1997/98, 3 folders (Box 118)
      - 1998/99
        - 1998/99, 2 folders (Box 118)
        - 1998/99 Big Ten Championship Manual and Releases (Box 118)
        - 1998/99 Programs (Box 118)
      - 1992/2000
        - 1999/2000 Tournament Brackets, 2 folders (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 Programs (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 Intercollegiate Tennis Association Rankings (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 Individual Results (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 Post Event Reports (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 News Releases (Box 118)
        - 1999/2000 Weekly Reports (Box 220)
        - 1999/2000 Big Ten Releases (Box 220)
        - 1999/2000 Newspaper Stories (Box 220)
      - 2000/02
        - 2000/01 Season Recap (Box 220)
        - 2000/01 Tournament Brackets (Box 220)
        - 2000/01 Programs (Box 220)
        - 2000/01 Intercollegiate Tennis Association Rankings (Box 220)
      - 2001/02
        - 2001/02 Season Recap (Box 220)
        - 2001/02 Tournament Brackets (Box 220)
        - 2001/02 Programs (Box 220)
      - 2002/03
        - 2002/03 Season Recap (Box 220)
        - 2002/03 Tournament Brackets (Box 220)
        - 2002/03 Programs (Box 220)
      - 2003/04
        - 2003/04 Season Recap (Box 220)
        - 2003/04 Tournament Brackets (Box 220)
        - 2003/04 Programs (Box 220)
  - Track-men
    - Media Guides, 1937-
      - 1937-1942, 1944 (Box 39)
      - 1945-1954 (Box 39)
      - 1955-1962 (Box 39)
      - 1963, 1965-1969 (Box 39)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 39)
      - 1970, 1973-1981 (Box 39)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 39)
      - 1988-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 39)
        (see box 70, women's track for combined 1991 media guide)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 39)
      - 1997-1999 (Box 39)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 39)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 39)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 39)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 39)
      - 2009 (Box 39)
    - Meet Programs and Results 1908-1989
      - Intercollegiate Association Amateur Athletics Meet 1908-1911, 1914 (Box 39)
        ("national championship meet," includes photos of many Michigan athletes in competition)
      - 1913 (Cornell, Syracuse, and Frosh-Soph meet, intramural) (Box 40)
      - 1921-1923, 1927, 1929 (Box 40)
      - 1935, 1937 (Box 40)
      - 1939-1942 (Box 40)
      - 1943-1944 (Box 40)
      - 1949-1951 (Box 40)
      - 1952-1959 (Box 40)
      - 1961-1965 (Box 40)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 40)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 40)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 40)
      - 1973 (Box 40)
      - 1974 (Box 40)
      - 1975 (Box 40)
      - 1976 (Box 40)
      - 1977 (Box 40)
      - 1978 (Box 40)
      - 1979 (Box 40)
      - 1980 (Box 40)
      - 1981 (Box 40)
      - 1982 (Box 40)
        (includes NCAA indoor meet held at UM)
      - 1983 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1983 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1984 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1984 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1985 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1985 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1986 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1986 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1987 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1987 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1988 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1988 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1989 indoor, 2 folders (Box 75)
      - 1989 outdoor, 3 folders (Box 75)
      - 1990 indoor (Box 75)
      - 1990 outdoor (Box 75)
      - 1991 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1991 outdoor, 2 folders (Box 216)
      - 1992 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1992 outdoor (Box 216)
      - 1993 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1993 outdoor (Box 216)
      - 1993 information (Box 216)
      - 1994 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1994 outdoor (Box 216)
      - 1994 News Release (Box 216)
      - 1995 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1995 outdoor (Box 216)
      - 1995 News Releases (Box 216)
      - 1996 indoor (Box 216)
      - 1996 outdoor (Box 217)
      - 1996 News Release (Box 217)
      - 1997 indoor, 2 folders (Box 217)
      - 1997 outdoor (Box 217)
      - 1998 indoor (Box 217)
      - 1998 outdoor (Box 217)
      - 1998 Meet Programs (Box 217)
      - 1998 News Release (Box 217)
      - 1999 indoor (Box 217)
      - 1999 outdoor (Box 217)
      - 2000 indoor (Box 217)
      - 2000 outdoor (Box 217)
      - 2000 News Release, 2 folders (Box 217)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 217)
      - 2001 News Release (Box 217)
    - Photographs 1885-1986
      - Team Photographs
        - Prints
          - 1895, 1929 (Box 41)
          - 1893, 1895 18961898 1900 (Box 7)
          - 1904-1907, 1909, 1912, 1913, 1914 (Box 7)
          - 1922-1923, 1930, 1938-1940 (Box 7)
          - 1951-1954, 1956-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 7)
          - 1970, 1973-1985, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
        - Negatives
          - 1893, 1895, 1900, 1903, 1904, 1926, 1970, 1973 1974(?), 1975 (Box 41)
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        - Coaches (Box 41)
        - Unidentified/undated (Box 41)
        - 1885 (Box 41)
        - 1898- circa 1905 "Niles Scrapbook" (Box 41)
          (magazine and newspaper photos of UM athletics teams, individuals, and meet action, including Archie Hahn; located in Box 8)
        - circa 1887-1905 unidentified (Box 41)
        - 1897-1900 (Box 41)
        - 1900-1903 meet action (Box 41)
        - 1901-1905, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - 1906-1919 (Box 41)
          (including portraits of coach Keene Fitzpatrick, see also programs from ICAA meet 1908-1911 and 1914 for photos of many Michigan competitors)
        - 1920-1926 (Box 41)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 41)
        - 1927-1929 (Box 41)
        - 1930-1934 (Box 41)
        - 1935-1937 (Box 41)
        - 1938-1942 (Box 41)
        - 1943-1944 (Box 41)
        - 1945-1951 (Box 41)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 41)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 41)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 41)
        - 1964-1966 (Box 41)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 41)
        - 1969 (Box 41)
        - 1970 (Box 41)
        - 1971, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - 1972 (Box 77)
        - 1973 (Box 77)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 77)
        - 1976 (Box 77)
        - 1977 (Box 77)
        - 1978 (Box 77)
        - 1979 (Box 77)
        - 1980 (Box 77)
        - 1981 (Box 77)
        - 1982 (Box 77)
        - 1983 (Box 77)
        - 1984 (Box 77)
        - 1985 (Box 77)
        - 1986 (Box 77)
        - 1987 (Box 77)
        - 1988 (Box 77)
        - 1990 (Box 77)
        - 1991 (Box 77)
        - 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1993 (Box 77)
        - 1994 (Box 77)
        - 1995 (Box 77)
        - 1996 (Box 77)
        - 1997 (Box 77)
        - 1998 (Box 77)
        - 1999 (Box 77)
        - 2000 (Box 77)
        - 2001 (Box 77)
        - 2002 (Box 77)
        - 2003 (Box 77)
        - 2001/02 (Box 261)
          - 2001/02 headshots, track and cross country (Box 261)
          - Len Paddock Invitational 5/10/2002, 2002 Men's Cross Country headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Len Paddock Invitational 5/10/2002-5/11/2002, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2002/03
          - Men's and Women's Track and Cross Country headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2003 Big Ten Outdoor 5/16/2003-5/18/2003., 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
            (1 optical disk may be bad)
        - 2003/04
          - Headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Red Simmons Invitational, (Joel Hakkon) 1/25/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Indoor Championship (Ann Arbor) 2/28/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Eastern Michigan Invitational 1/17/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
            (CDs may be bad)
          - 2004 NCAA Indoor Championships Championship (men and women) (Box 261)
          - NCAA Track and Field and Cross Country 2004 (Box 261)
            (photos from mensracing.com, includes 2004 NCAA distance medley, shots of Nick Willis, Nate Brannen, Tim Broe and Kevin Sullivan)
          - NCAA Outdoor Championships (Box 261)
            (Robert Black photos)
          - Len Paddock Invitational, (M&W) 5/7/2004, 5/8/2004, 6 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships, 5/14/2004-5/126/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - NCAA Outdoor Championships, 6/9/2004-6/12/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2003/04 UM NCAA C Champions (Box 261)
            (M Track, M Swimming, W Gymnastics posed on granite M)
        - 2004/05
          - "Day in the Life of Nate Brannen" 03/15/2005 (Box 261)
          - 2005 headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2005 Men's Track Images (Box 261)
            (compiled cd, includes headshots and action for individuals)
          - Jack Harvey Invitational 1/8/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Silverston Invitational 2/19/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - U-M at NCAA Indoor Championship 3/11/2005-3/12/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
            (photos by Alison Wade/New York Road Runners)
          - Len Paddock Invitational, 5/6/2005=5-7/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships, 5/14/2005=5/15/2005, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - NCAA Championships (M & W), 6/8/2005-6/11/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
            (Robert I. Black photographer)
          - Penn Relays 4/29/2005-4/30/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2005/06
          - Team and headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2006 Media guide cover and poster photos (Box 261)
          - Jack Harvey Invitational 1/7/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - NCAA Indoor Championships (M & W) 3/10/2006-3/11/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Central Collegiate Championship 4/22/2006, cs only (Box 261)
          - Len Paddock Invitational 5/5/2006-5/6/2006, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships 5/12/2006-5/14/2006, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2006/07
          - 2007 team and headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2006 All-Americans, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Eastern Michigan Invitational 4/21/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Red Simmons Invitational 2/19/2007, cs only (Box 261)
          - 2007 Track Hall of Fame Banquet, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2007/08
          - Team photo and headshots 10/18/2007 (Box 261)
          - Simmons/Harvey Invitational 1/26/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Silverston Invitational 2/23/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - "The Dual" UM-OSU 1/19/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Adam Harris interview 2/12/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Len Paddock Invitational, 5/9/2008-5/10/2008, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships 5/16/2008-5/18/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
            [Copyright Walt Middleton Photography]
          - NCAA Mideast Regional (M & W) 5/30/2008-5/31/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - NCAA Championships (M & W) 6/11/2008-6/14/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - 2008 Senior Dinner, 5/19/2008 (Box 261)
          - Track and Field Camp (M & W) 6/23/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2008/09
          - Team photo, player headshot and coaches, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - UM-OSU DUAL meet 1/17/2009, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Simmons-Harvey Invitational 2/24/2009, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Silverston Invitational 2/21/2009, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Indoor Meet 2/28/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Meet 5/15/2009-5/17/2009 (Box 261)
          - NCAA Mideast Regional Meet 5/29/2009-5/30/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 261)
        - 2011/2012
          - Big Ten Outdoor Meet, BTN feature 5/11/2012, 2 optical disks DVDs
          - Michigan Athletes at London Olympic Games 2012
            (Geena Gall, Jeff Porter, Nate Brannen, Nick Willis, Nicole Sifuentes, Tiffany Porter)
        - Action shots of Charles Fonville, and Cedric(?) Smith (Box 7)
  - Wrestling
    - Media Guides
      - 1938-1942, 1950, 1952-1958 (Box 44)
      - 1960-1962, 1964-1968 (Box 44)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 44)
      - 1971/72-1974/75 (Box 44)
      - 1976/77-1979/80 (Box 44)
      - 1980/81-1988/89 (Box 44)
        (missing 1981/82)
      - 1989/90-1991/92 (Box 44)
      - 1992/93-1993/94 (Box 44)
      - 1994/95-1995/96 (Box 44)
      - 1996/97 (Box 44)
      - 1997/98 (Box 44)
        (includes post-season guide)
      - 1998/99 (Box 44)
      - 1999/00-2000/01 (Box 44)
      - 2001/02-2002/03 (Box 44)
      - 2003/04-2004/05 (Box 44)
      - 2005/06-2006/2007 (Box 44)
    - Compiled Season and Match Results, 1923-19
      - Overall Results and standings 1926-1974 (Box 44)
      - 1923/24-1962/63 (Box 44)
      - 1963/64-1975/76 (Box 44)
      - 1976/77-1986/87 (Box 44)
      - 1987/88-1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - Prints
          - 1945, 1952/53, 1953/54, 1958/59-1960/61, 1963/64-1965/66, 1967/68-1969/70, 1971/72-1974/75, 1976/77-1978/79, 1980/81-1981/82 (Box 45)
          - 1983-1992 (Box 45)
          - 1992/93-1996/97, 1998/99-2002/03 2004/05-06 (Box 45)
        - Negatives
          - 1968/69, 1970/71, 1977/78, 2000/01 (Box 45)
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - Conference and national champions (Box 45)
          (4x5 copy prints, originals of some were damaged, does not include all champions)
        - 1926-1927 (Box 45)
        - 1925-1959 (Box 45)
        - 1959/60-1961/62 (Box 45)
        - 1962/63 (Box 45)
        - 1963/64-1966/67 (Box 45)
        - 1967/68-1968/69 (Box 45)
        - 1969/70 (Box 45)
        - 1970/71 (Box 45)
        - 1971/72 (Box 45)
        - 1972/73 (Box 45)
        - 1973/74 (Box 45)
        - 1974/75 (Box 45)
        - 1975/76 (Box 45)
        - 1976/77 (Box 45)
        - 1977/78 (Box 45)
        - 1978/79 (Box 45)
        - 1979/80 (Box 45)
          (also includes color photo of Steve Fraser at 1988 Olympics, 2 color prints and 8x10 color transparency)
        - 1980/81 (Box 45)
        - 1981/82 (Box 45)
        - 1982/83 (Box 45)
        - 1983/84 (Box 45)
        - 1984/85 (Box 45)
        - 1985/86 (Box 45)
        - 1986/87 (Box 45)
        - 1987/88 (Box 45)
        - 1988/89 (Box 45)
        - 1989/90 (Box 76)
        - 1990/91 (Box 76)
        - 1991/92, cs, prints, head shots (Box 76)
        - 1992/93, cs, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1993/94, cs, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1994/95, cs, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1995/96, cs, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1996/97, cs, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1997/98, cs, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 1998/99, print, meet action (Box 76)
        - 1999/2000, cs, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 2000/01, cs, negatives, prints, head shots, meet action, posed (Box 76)
        - 2000/01
          - Eastern Michigan Open 11/3/2000, 1 cd (Box 76)
        - 2001/02
          - Portraits and posed action, contact sheet (Box 76)
          - 2002/03 Season Disc ( (Box 76)
          - Central Michigan University, 12/8/20001, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Lehigh 1/4/2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - 2001/02 Historical Wrestling Photographs, black & white and color scans, meet action (Box 76)
          - 2001/02 Wrestling Picnic (Box 76)
        - 2002/03
          - Player head shots and posed action, 1 cd and contact sheet, Photo Services tiff (Box 76)
          - Wrestling Photos Compilation disc 1 (Box 76)
            (Headshot, coaches, Team picture, Cleveland State, Midlands, team picnic)
          - Wrestling Photos Compilation disc #2 (Box 76)
            (includes Indiana, Ohio State, Penn State, Big Ten, NCAA)
          - Cleveland State University 12/14/2002, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Illinois 1/24/2003, meet action (Box 76)
          - Indiana 1/31/2003, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Ohio State 2/16/203, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Penn State 2/15/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
        - 2003/04
          - Portraits and posed action, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Central Michigan, 111/23/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Lehigh 11/23/2003, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Cliff Keen Las Vegas Invitational 12/5/2003, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Eastern Michigan 12/14/2003, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Iowa, 1/232004, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 76)
          - Minnesota 1/24/2004, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 76)
          - Wisconsin 2/15/2004, 1 cd, contact sheets (Box 76)
          - NCAA Meet, 3/182004 (Box 76)
            (also includes some Wisconsin meet and golf outing)
        - 2004/05
          - Headshots and Posed Action, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 76)
          - Cliff Keen Invitational,12/32004, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Cleveland State, 12/10/2004, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - CMU 1/2/2004, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Penn State 1/14/2005, 1 cd, contact sheet (Box 76)
          - Ohio State 2/6/2005, 2 optical disks cds, contact sheets, Photo services (Box 76)
          - Illinois 2/14/2005, 2cds and contact sheet Photo services (Box 76)
          - Purdue 2/20/2005, 1 cd, contact sheets (Box 76)
          - Miscellaneous 2004/05, 1 cd (Box 76)
            (includes team at NCAA)
          - Compilation Discs, 2 optical disks cds (Box 76)
        - 2005/06
          - Headshots and posed action, team photo, contact sheets (Box 76)
          - Cliff Keen, Las Vegas 12/5/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Lehigh 1/8/2006, 1 cd, contact sheets (Box 76)
          - Nebraska 1/14/2006, 1 cd, contact sheets (Box 76)
          - Northwestern 1/28/2006, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 76)
          - Michigan State 1/29/2006, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 76)
          - NCAA 2006, 1 cd (Box 76)
          - Cornel 2005 National Duals, 2006 NCAA 2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 76)
          - Wrestling Trophies (Box 76)
          - 2005/06 Wrestling Covers, 1 cd, pdf, ind, and unidentified files of media guide (Box 76)
          - 2005/06 Wrestling Inside Covers, 1 cd, eps and xps files (Box 76)
          - 2005/06 Wrestling Poster, 1 cd, pdf, ind, and unidentified files (Box 76)
    - Meet Programs and Results
      - 1934, 1940, 1959 (Box 204)
      - 1959/60-1965/66 (Box 204)
      - 1966/67-1967/68 (Box 204)
      - 1968/69-1969/70 (Box 204)
      - 1970/71-1972/73 (Box 204)
      - 1973/74-1974/75 (Box 204)
      - 1976/77-1978/79 (Box 204)
      - 1979/80-1980/81 (Box 204)
      - 1981/82 (Box 204)
      - 1982/83 (Box 204)
      - 1983/84 (Box 204)
      - 1984/85 (Box 204)
        (includes program for 1985 US Greco-Roman Championships with feature on Steve Fraser)
      - 1986/87 (Box 204)
      - 1987/88, 2 folders (Box 204)
      - 1988/89, 3 folders (Box 204)